{
  "questions": [
    {
      "questionNumber": 1,
      "questionText": "What is the capital city of the Philippines?",
      "correctAnswer": "Manila",
      "wrongAnswers": [ "Laguna", "Cavite", "Batangas" ]
    },
    {
      "questionNumber": 2,
      "questionText": "What is the famous rice dish often considered the national food of the Philippines?",
      "correctAnswer": "Adobo",
      "wrongAnswers": [ "Sinigang", "Kaldereta" ]
    },
    {
      "questionNumber": 3,
      "questionText": "Which volcano is known as the 'Perfect Cone' and is located in the Philippines?",
      "correctAnswer": "Mayon Volcano",
      "wrongAnswers": [ "Bulkang Taal", "Mt. Pinatubo" ]
    },
    {
      "questionNumber": 4,
      "questionText": "What is the traditional Filipino folk dance often performed at celebrations and gatherings?",
      "correctAnswer": "Tinikling",
      "wrongAnswers": [ "Hip Hop", "Break dance" ]
    },
    {
      "questionNumber": 5,
      "questionText": "What is the name of the largest shopping mall in the Philippines, located in Metro Manila?",
      "correctAnswer": "SM Mall of Asia",
      "wrongAnswers": [ "SM Sta.Rosa", "SM Calamba", "SM San Pedro" ]
    }
  ],

  "questions1": [
    {
      "questionNumber": 1,
      "questionText": "What is the capital city of the awawawaw?",
      "correctAnswer": "Manila",
      "wrongAnswers": [ "Laguna", "Cavite", "Batangas" ]
    },
    {
      "questionNumber": 2,
      "questionText": "awdadgeadwesgsefsefefs?",
      "correctAnswer": "Adobo",
      "wrongAnswers": [ "Sinigang", "Kaldereta" ]
    },
    {
      "questionNumber": 3,
      "questionText": "nthhtfhdgrdfsfsefesfssefsefesfse?",
      "correctAnswer": "Mayon Volcano",
      "wrongAnswers": [ "Bulkang Taal", "Mt. Pinatubo" ]
    },
    {
      "questionNumber": 4,
      "questionText": "azerhshaegagagaagea?",
      "correctAnswer": "Tinikling",
      "wrongAnswers": [ "Hip Hop", "Break dance" ]
    },
    {
      "questionNumber": 5,
      "questionText": "Fawefaewfawfwafwafafeafafew?",
      "correctAnswer": "SM Mall of Asia",
      "wrongAnswers": [ "SM Sta.Rosa", "SM Calamba", "SM San Pedro" ]
    }
  ]
}
